迈克 · 诺斯: 下面是我们将要学习的内容的大概轮廓。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So here's a rough
outline of what we're gonna learn.
我们将从一个类似于打字稿编程的速成课程开始
We're gonna start out with kind of a crash
course in the TypeScript programming
语言。
language.
现在，我们没有时间，这不是一个好的利用我们的时间
Now, we don't have time, and
it's not a good use of our time
详细介绍了打字稿所能做到的每一个方面。
to go through every little facet of
what can be done with TypeScript.
我在这里的主要目标是确保我留给你们一个伟大的精神
My main goal here is to ensure that
I leave you with a great mental
如何思考这种编程语言的模型。
model of how to think about
this programming language.
因为这样你就可以
Because then you can go and
你可以了解所有我做的没有被你碰过的小角落。
you can learn about all the little corners
that I made left untouched on your own.
我们将学习如何配置打字稿编译器。
We'll learn about configuring
the TypeScript compiler.
这一点很重要，因为它可以是缩小的区别
This is important because it can be
the difference between shrinking
你的代码增加了70% ，对吗？
your code by 70%, right?
就像如果你正在为 IE6构建代码，那里有很多额外的代码，因为我们不能
Like if you're building for IE6, there's
a lot of extra code there because we can't
真的取决于我们在浏览器中使用的东西。
really depend on as much being
there in the browser for us to use.
它还可以帮助你设置严格的设置。
And it also helps you set
your strictness settings.
所以如果你真的想要类型安全，你必须这样做
So if you really want type safety,
you kind of have to
把事情安排得恰到好处，这样规矩才有力度，对吧？
set things appropriately so
the rules are strong, right?
我们将经过三个步骤，实际的战略
We will go through a three step,
practical strategy for
从打字稿转换到 JavaScript。
converting from TypeScript to JavaScript.
这样做有很多不好的方法。
There are bad ways to do this.
如果做得对如果做得像我教你的那样,
If done correctly, and
if done the way that I'm gonna teach you,
这可能是一个非常平稳，渐进的过程。
it can be a very smooth,
incremental process.
这不一定是一个大的，破坏性的事情，对吗？
It doesn't have to be a big,
disruptive thing, right?
我们不必像重写 JavaScript 一样对待它
We don't have to treat it like
we're rewriting a JavaScript
用 Swift 或其他完全不相关的语言编写程序。
program in Swift or
something completely unrelated.
我们可以利用这些语言之间的相似性。
We can take advantage of the similarity
between these languages.
混合 JavaScript 和 TypeScript 模块的能力。
And the ability for mixing JavaScript and
TypeScript modules.
我们将更多地关注高级类型和泛型。
We'll focus quite a bit on
advanced types and generics.
你可以把泛型看作是参数化的类型,
And you can think of generics
as parameterized types, right,
我们将一个值传递给一个函数来对值进行排序。
we pass a value to a function to
sort of parameterize the value.
我们可以将类型参数传递给泛型，来参数化类型,
We can pass type parameters to generics,
to parameterize types,
就像填补空白一样。
like a fill-in-the-blank
kind of situation.
最后，我想给你们一个简短的
And at the end, I want to give you a quick
演示了打字稿编译器如何查看你的代码。
demo of how the TypeScript
compiler looks at your code.
所以我们将使用 JavaScript API 来编译打字稿,
So we're going to use the JavaScript API
for the TypeScript compiler,
不是因为我认为你们很多人最终会在应用程序中使用它。
not because I think a lot of you
will end up using this in your apps.
但是它允许我们在引擎盖下面挑选
But it allows us to
pick under the hood and
看看打字稿是如何理解我们的代码的。
to see how TypeScript
understands our code.
以及它是如何将它分开，以及它是如何在数据结构中表示它的。
And how it sort of splits it apart and
how it represents it in data structures.
这一点非常重要，以便确认您拥有正确的
That's really important in order to
validate that you have the correct
心理模型。
mental model.